{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Hibbert_Tupper",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1855-08-03",
    "human_readable": "Charles Hibbert Tupper was born on August 3rd, 1855.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887604713439941,
            "question": "Is Charles Hibbert Tupper's birthdate August 3rd, 1855?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9460403323173523,
            "question": "On which day of August was Charles Hibbert Tupper born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9312513470649719,
            "question": "When was Charles Hibbert Tupper born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9239183664321899,
            "question": "Who was born on August 3rd, 1855?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233303666114807,
            "question": "Which person was born in 1855 on August 3rd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.860788881778717,
            "question": "What is the birthdate of Charles Hibbert Tupper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8307861685752869,
            "question": "What is Charles Hibbert Tupper's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8149140477180481,
            "question": "Who is associated with the date August 3rd, 1855?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.613815426826477,
            "question": "In what year did Charles Hibbert Tupper come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5769026279449463,
            "question": "August 3rd is the birthday of whom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Hibbert Tupper was born on August 3rd, 1855.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7289_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Charles Hibbert Tupper come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7289_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is associated with the date August 3rd, 1855?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7289_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Charles Hibbert Tupper's birth date?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7289_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7289_40.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Charles Hibbert Tupper was born in Halifax, Nova Scotia, on August 3, 1855,\" which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}